{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622531","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622531","name":"Little Caesars Arena- West Club","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Detroit District Sportservice","licenseNumber":"220979","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.05500,42.34103","geojson":{"id":"51622531","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.054995648,42.341031121]},"properties":{"name":"Little Caesars Arena- West Club","owner":"Detroit District Sportservice","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"220979","establishmentid":"51622531","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"18/4/2022"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622532","name":"Little Caesars Event Level Commissary","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622533","name":"Little Caesars Arena- Pistons Dining","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622528","name":"Little Caesars Arena- Club Level Concess","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622530","name":"Little Caesars Arena- Dough Room","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622508","name":"Little Caesar's District Market","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622509","name":"Little Caesars Arena Kid Rock Made in De","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622510","name":"Little Caesars Arena- Portables","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622526","name":"Little Caesars Arena- District Market","address":"2645 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622529","name":"Little Caesars Arena- East Club","address":"2645  Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622534","name":"Little Caesars Arena- Players Club West ","address":"2645 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61729","inspectionDate":"2023-03-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Single-service/use items","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"CHEMICAL STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"57065","inspectionDate":"2022-01-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"BAR (RIGHT)","subLocation":"Inside the Handwashing soap","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Missing Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"50806","inspectionDate":"2020-02-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"PIZZA PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"In large container","location":"PIZZA PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44215","inspectionDate":"2018-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PIZZA PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING CABINET","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"handwash","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40635","inspectionDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING CABINET","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"CARVING STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622531"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}